

張育誠 (Chang Yu Chen)

I am a professional software developer with over 7 years of experience and a B.S. degree in Computer Science.

Proficient in C#, TypeScript, and Python.

Skilled in Asp.Net, Django/FastAPI, and Node.js.

Strong problem-solving, system design, and learning skills. I excel at working in teams and have experience as a team manager. I possess strong collaborative and communication abilities, as well as extensive cross-group coordination skills.

https://makotoatsu.github.io

) <u>https://github.com/MakotoAtsu</u>

chris03152008@gmail.com

Experience

Senior Backend Developer

Pinkoi • Feb. 2023 - Current

Senior Backend Developer

KooBits • Apr. 2022 - Aug. 2022

- Introduced Unit Testing into two services and enabled Test-Driven Development.
- · Implemented the Unit of Work pattern to address issues with excessive database connection usage.
- Integrated GitHub Actions to enable CI/CD after creating a pull request.

Software Team Lead

PIXIS • Mar. 2019 - Mar. 2022

- · Led product development within the team for a comprehensive solution of Network Access Control, IPAM, and Device Discovery.
- Dockerized the product, reducing network probe software IP occupancy by 45%.
- · Introduced HAProxy and Redis to enable high availability characteristics for the
- · Separated the frontend and backend, introducing a JS framework (Vue.js) and modern software architecture to expedite development time.
- Transitioned from .Net Framework to .Net Core, enhancing both the product's performance and security.
- Built a new Custom Report feature, providing users with the ability to create various reports.
- Managed support of 802.1x dynamic VLAN assignment and strengthened product competitiveness.
- Optimized loading performance and increased concurrent usage by 30% every 30 minutes.
- Created a CI/CD pipeline, which shortened the product development life cycle.



Taipei, Taiwan



A Mandarin , English



pinkoi

KooBits*

PIXIS



Senior Software Engineer

Macronix International Co., Ltd • Feb. 2016 - Mar. 2019

- Designed and improved automation software for semiconductor equipment.
- Independently developed 15 Equipment Automation Programs (EAPs) from the ground up, enabling automatic product measurement and report-data upload.
- Managed and implemented proofs of concept (POCs) for 9 EAPs to automate equipment recipe selection and production.
- Enhanced 54 EAPs based on user demands.
- Developed a Dynamic Calculation system, allowing users to create their own calculation formulas.
- Constructed a new system enabling the Manufacturing Department to collect and control all factory equipment information in real-time.



Firmware Developer (Intern)

Whetron Electronics Co., Ltd. • Jul. 2014 - Jul. 2015

- Developed and maintained firmware for parking sensors.
- Constructed and implemented testing tools for products.
- Built a new testing tool for smart keys, facilitating quicker and more precise product testing execution by operators.

Education



I-SHOU University (ISU)

B.S, 2016

Computer Science and Information Engineering

Skill

Programming Language

- C# .Net
- Python
- TypeScript (JavaScript)

Programming Ability

- RESTful API Design
- OOD / Design Pattern
- System Design

Framework

- Backend
 - ASP.NET Core
 - Node.js
 - Django/FastAPI
- Frontend
 - Vue.js
 - React.js
- ORM
 - Entity Framework
 - Dapper
- UnitTest
 - XUnit
 - Mocha/Jest
 - Pytest

Domain Knowledge

- Network Protocol
 - TCP/IP
 - ARP
 - SNMP
 - o 802.1Q
 - o 802.1X
- Authentication/Authorization
 - OAuth2
 - OpenId Connect
- Container
 - Docker
 - Docker-Compose
 - MACVLAN

Tools

- Database
 - SQL Server
 - MySQL
 - Redis
 - MongoDB
- Network
 - Wireshark
 - Tcpdump
 - Nmap
- CI/CD
 - Azure DevOps
 - Github Action

References

Clarence Wu

Senior Back-End Developer

Clarence@koobits.com

in linkedin.com/in/clarence-wu-8889a768

Shih-En Tsai

Senior Back-End Developer

Shihen@koobits.com

in linkedin.com/in/4n-tsai

Hank Chen

Assistant Manager

Hank@pixis.com.tw

Larry Tang

Principle Software Engineer

Larry@pixis.com.tw

in linkedin.com/in/家倫-湯-ab8b61bb